Murni .
Murni !
- Bring the flowers here . - Yes .
What is it ?
Were you daydreaming ?
I 'm not feeling well .
May I be excused ?
Yes , of course .
Where do I put the noodles ?
On the table over there .
- What is it ? - What 's wrong ?
- They 're rotten . - What ?
The noodles were only just done , but there are maggots all over them .
Ma 'am ?
- Is the rain shaman here ? - Yes .
I saw him with Darmo .
Kohar is lucky , getting to marry the headman 's daughter .
At least he won 't have to worry about getting a job .
Yes , but poor Murni . She must be heartbroken .
Nah , she was just confused .
She shouldn 't have fallen in love with a playboy like him .
But he 's handsome and good with words .
Excuse me , sir .
Is someone sabotaging us ?
I 've fasted for five days . Why is it about to rain ?
What is happening ?
What is this ?
- What 's going on ? - I don 't know .
- Why am I levitating ? Help me . - What is this ?
Baidah .
Baidah ?
Don 't kill me ! Don 't ! It 's not my fault !
- It was all Father 's doing ! - Baidah , calm down !
Calm down , this is your father .
Baidah , this is Kohar .
Don 't be scared .
- Baidah . - I 'm scared !
Mother !
Calm down , it 's nothing .
There are no snakes !
I 'm scared !
Mother .
- Get the shaman . - Yes , sir .
Snakes !
- Help ! - Get inside the house !
Help !
To the west - -
West ?
Right .
She lives in the west .
It must be her .
Who ?
It 's her .
Gentlemen , my wife was driven mad ,
and the shaman who was treating my wife was killed .
As civilized people , we cannot let this go .
Today ,
misfortune befell me .
The same might happen to you tomorrow .
I can 't believe disaster could enter this house just like that .
Are you going to let this evil run amok ?
- No ! - I didn 't think so .
Let 's go to Murni 's house now .
- Agreed ! - And we will bring her here .
Kohar , don 't act rashly .
You need to find out the truth .
Once I drag Murni here , we will . You will thank me later .
- Let 's go ! - Hurry !
Mother .
Please don 't be mad at me .
I 'm not a virgin anymore .
He took that away from me .
Murni ...
The thing that you should have valued most was your dignity .
Please forgive me , Mother .
Forgive me .
He seduced me .
Kohar promised that he 'd marry me .
If your father were still alive ,
and if your brother were here ,
this would not have happened .
Mother , it was my fault .
I didn 't refuse .
Please forgive your daughter .
You 're the only one I have .
You are the only one who loves me .
My dear daughter .
Let 's just leave it to God .
Let 's pray now .
What is going on , Kohar ?
You have practiced black magic .
Get her .
Are you crazy ?
Black magic ? I did not do that !
You 're an asshole , Kohar . You 're a liar !
Let me go !
What did she do wrong ?
She 's already miserable enough .
Let go ! Let her go !
Get out of the way !
No , Kohar !
- Drag her out . - Let 's go !
- Mother ! - Murni !
Mother !
Kohar , what did Murni do ? Why are they hitting her ?
Please , Kohar .
Make it stop . Don 't hurt her .
I beg you .
In God 's name , I beg you .
Please don 't hurt her .
Set it on fire !
Let 's go !
Come on , let 's go .
Mother !
- Mother ! - Hey ! Move .
Murni !
Let 's go . Stop fighting !
Mother !
Stop .
Throw her down .
I thought we were taking her to the office ?
We have to make sure we get rid of the black magic !
- Throw her off the cliff ! - Yes , sir .
Kohar ! Don 't !
Kohar , you 're so evil !
It 's all right .
You 're in a house that belongs to someone who doesn 't hate you .
You 're free from the torture of those evil people .
You shouldn 't move too much .
Just stay in bed .
Last night , you were talking in your sleep .
You mentioned Kohar .
Who is he ?
He incited the villagers to harm me .
What 's his problem ?
I don 't know .
I just heard that he thinks I performed black magic on his wife ,
and on the shaman who was supposed to treat her .
But honestly ,
it wasn 't me .
He was lying .
I 'm disappointed by his actions , but I 've never wanted to do such a thing .
I 'd never use black magic .
Why are you disappointed ?
He betrayed me .
Oh , Murni .
You believe your neighbors ,
but you don 't believe your own lover ?
It 's not true .
How could I fall for Baidah ?
Everyone knows what type of woman Baidah is .
She got pregnant without a husband . She 's a flirt .
Who knows ?
Men tend to like flirtatious women .
Kohar ...
That tickles .
You said it won 't be long ?
Murni , I love you .
Kohar ...
We shouldn 't have done this now .
I wasn 't planning on losing my virginity here .
Murni , it makes no difference .
Be it here or in our bed , it 's the same thing .
And you will end up being mine anyway .
Don 't worry .
And I have proven
that you are still a virgin .
I have nothing to look forward to on my first night .
Please don 't think of me as someone easy because of this .
Trust me , Murni .
We 'll get married soon .
He didn 't keep his promise .
He ended up marrying the headman 's daughter .
And not only that ...
I was still heartbroken over it ,
yet he came to my house and accused me of something horrible .
He accused me of using black magic .
And the rest
you already know .
I swear to God , I didn 't do it .
I 'm not that evil .
Do not mention that name here .
It is bad luck .
You 've been tortured .
You have to get revenge .
Who else has hurt you ?
Who else has made you suffer ?
Pay them back .
They accused you of using black magic ?
Then just practice it .
Curse all those people in that village .
Sir ...
I don 't want to do that .
I 'll let God judge them in the afterlife .
God is just .
Do not mention that name here .
You have to do it .
You 're not a goddess who is not allowed to get revenge .
You have suffered .
If it hadn 't been for me , you would already be dead .
Will you let those people who intended to kill you live happily ?
And will you let the headman who let his people torture you
run the village ?
I don 't understand black magic . Or voodoo .
I will teach you black magic .
I will make you the queen of black magic .
To get revenge .
What 's wrong ?
I don 't know .
Isn 't that Murni ?
- The one who is supposed to be dead . - Right .
I was one of the people who threw her off the cliff .
Maybe that 's her ghost .
Cold drinks !
- Her feet are on the ground . - Yeah .
That means she 's not a ghost .
Besides , ghosts don 't go out in the afternoon .
You 're right .
I have to go . My boss might be looking for me .
You shouldn 't be such a pushover .
Now you 're running for your life .
Here you go .
Wait for me !
Move aside !
Hurry !
Help !
Murni ! Help !
Kohar ! Murni came back to life .
She 's furious .
Pungut was cursed and his face was wrecked !
Thankfully , I know some spells , so I was safe .
Stop saying nonsense , Darmo .
It 's true , Kohar .
Who could survive being thrown off the cliff ? She must be dead .
Then she 's come back to life !
I swear .
Or maybe that was her spirit ?
I don 't know .
I 'm sure she 's going to look for you , Kohar .
I didn 't hurt her . The villagers did .
But they did it because you made them .
And you 're the only one who had a relationship with Murni .
I 'm not afraid .
Any ghost can come for me if they dare .
You 'll see .
I went to his house .
His body was covered in scabies .
It was rotten and it smelled bad .
Darmo thinks that everyone who joined in on hitting Murni
will get what they deserve .
- Really ? - Yes .
I have to go now .
- How much is it ? - What did you order ?
- Just coffee . - That will be 200 .
See you .
It 's Murni !
Ghosts are difficult to conquer ,
but we cannot give up .
We have to get rid of all evil !
- Agree ! - No !
No !
You 're the evil one !
You betrayed Murni .
You took her virginity .
And then you lied and accused her of something horrible !
If there is evil in this world ,
then it is you , Kohar !
You 're the devil !
You 're a liar !
You betrayed her !
You 're just like your daughter , old lady !
Take that !
Stay out of this !
Shut your mouth !
Keep going .
Keep going !
I was expecting this .
You have destroyed my family .
You burned down my house .
You killed my daughter .
And now , you 're going to kill me .
Kill me !
What a fuss .
Kohar ! Are you out of your mind ?
Why would you hit an old lady ?
You need to go to the police .
Her daughter practices black magic .
That means she does it , too .
Get up .
- Enough , Kohar ! - What now ?
You 've crossed the line !
Asshole .
Now , everyone who refuses to become victims of black magic
like the other two villagers , come with me .
No !
I 'm the headman of this village .
This is not how you all should act .
I don 't want history to repeat itself .
This is a state of law .
Every matter should be resolved legally .
The law requires proof , sir .
But practices like black magic
cannot be easily proven .
And the consequences of those acts are worse for us .
I 'm sorry .
I have to disagree with you .
Let 's go .
Let 's go , move .
Murni does not practice
black magic .
What is going on ?
- Excuse me . - Yes ?
- Where did the ghost go ? - I 'm not sure .
I was so terrified .
We have to find her lair . Maybe it 's in the cliff .
- Now ? But it 's late . - Yes .
What are we waiting for ?
You should eat .
I have bad news .
I just attended the funeral
of the person you love the most .
Your mother .
I never told you to become a murderer .
But what they did forced you to become one .
An eye for an eye
and a tooth for a tooth .
Everything has consequences .
Everyone gets what they deserve .
Wait , what ?
What 's happening ?
Jo ! Help me , Jo !
- Oh no ! - This must be Murni 's doing !
Forgive me , Murni .
Dear .
There , there .
Now , go to bed .
Mother !
Who is this cutie pie ?
It 's okay , dear .
Little one , please don 't cry
Little one , don 't you cry
Little one , you 're very beautiful
I want to hug - -
Oh , okay .
Go on , drink .
That 's enough .
Kohar ?
What ?
Give the baby back .
PRAYER ROOM
Are you here to pray ?
Is this prayer room abandoned ?
Well , it is used sometimes .
But the villagers here aren 't consistent .
They only pray when they are miserable .
Once the harvest season comes , they forget .
Oh , right , where are you from ?
The city .
It seems like
something wrong is happening in this village .
- Meaning ? - Well , they seem frightened .
They get suspicious of foreigners like me .
I was actually born here .
You aren 't wrong .
This village is - -
Listen .
Let me tell you .
You 'd better leave this place .
Holy verses don 't work on black magic .
I 'm telling the truth .
That 's weird .
You should know
that black magic won 't work on holy verses .
Why don 't you pray ?
Ouch !
Ugh .
I 've asked around ,
but people refuse to help .
It 's okay .
It will be okay .
Siti !
You 're back !
Thank God .
Oh , dear .
My baby .
There , there .
Don 't cry .
Don 't go out at night .
- It 's just a friend 's house . - Go inside .
Don 't make me walk too fast .
- They saw Murni . - Really ? Where ?
Where is the place , exactly ?
- This business with - - - What business ?
Hurry up , Din .
I think it 's over there .
- This is our village 's problem . - That 's right .
Hurry up , Din .
Can I get some coffee , please ?
We 're closing .
I 've been traveling , and I don 't have family here .
Can I just have something to drink ?
Please ?
Give him a drink , Nem .
He 's a traveler .
Why is it so quiet ?
It 's not even that late .
Who would want to go out just to be cursed with misfortune ?
This village is in danger .
A couple of villagers became victims of black magic .
And it seems like all of the people are going to be killed off one by one .
Who did this ? What happened ?
- Two fried bananas and a cup of coffee . - Five hundred .
What 's wrong ?
Don 't be afraid .
By God 's will , we will be safe as long as you tell me who did this .
You will find out eventually if you plan on staying here .
Honestly , I 'm too afraid to tell you .
I 'm scared I might get cursed
if I say something wrong .
I advise you to leave this village .
Don 't involve yourself in the madness that is happening here .
I was born here .
I 'd like to know what happened to the villagers .
Believe me , son , that will not benefit you at all .
If you take one wrong step , it might cost you your life .
- What is this place ? - This is a haunted area .
Yes , I heard about that .
I heard that , too .
- Are you ready ? - It 's already late .
- What - - - What is that ?
Move !
- Hey ! - Forward ! Let 's go forward !
Don 't run , stay and witness this !
I will put an end to that black magic lady !
Stop it , Murni .
Please .
Forgive me .
Stop !
Murni !
This is dangerous .
Murni really has become a queen of black magic .
I 'm worried .
- Kohar might die , sir . - That 's true .
You need to quickly report this .
If not , Kohar will become another victim .
We were all attacked by a strong wind , and we were helpless .
That 's true , sir .
This is hard .
I told you not to act rashly .
That 's because I was finding someone who can fight against black magic .
That 's Kohar !
- Kohar ? - It 's Kohar !
Help him ! Quickly ! Come on .
Kohar ! What happened to you ?
Help him , please !
- Quick , get a shaman or a cleric ! - Okay .
This must be black magic .
I don 't know what to do . Do we even have a cleric ?
Our shaman is dead .
Help ! Quick !
Get her inside .
Kill that damn headman .
Sir !
What 's wrong ?
What happened ?
What 's happening ?
What is it ?
What is going on ?
Black magic ! The headman is in danger !
Can I borrow your sarong ?
Thank you , son .
If it weren 't for you ,
I don 't know what would have happened .
You should thank God .
Thank God you were here .
When I met you this afternoon , I knew
that you were a powerful person .
I can tell .
You look calm and wise .
I don 't have any powers .
But I am sure that every evil can be defeated by God 's knowledge .
Anyone can defeat black magic if they believe in Him .
The headman said that the man is young ,
but he 's more powerful than our previous shaman .
Yeah , Darmo said the same thing .
He 's Santri . He practices Islam .
People have started praying again .
Darmo .
This is what a village should look like .
A prayer room , and people who use it to pray .
If there are still people who recite the Koran every day ,
then there is hope that this village will be free from misfortune .
That 's right .
I 've killed Kohar .
I feel satisfied now .
The wrath that I have kept in my chest
is now gone .
Not yet .
You haven 't punished the other people
who hurt you .
Every single one of them .
Including the people who indirectly
killed your mother .
My only enemy is Kohar .
The others don 't matter to me .
I want to leave this village .
Maybe go to the city ,
or another village where the people don 't know who Murni is .
You will be more miserable .
People in this village can be vicious .
They have all been calling you the queen of black magic .
You won 't be accepted by society anywhere .
Anywhere .
You must continue to curse this village
and kill every person in this village
until Headman Sabri kneels down in front of you and me .
Then you and I will run this village .
I don 't think I can do that .
They 're just followers .
They didn 't do anything wrong .
Kohar was the one who persuaded them with his rotten mouth .
You need to remember one thing .
The magic that I taught you
will eat you up if you don 't use it on someone else .
Hey , who does this belong to ?
Hello !
Who 's taking a bath there ?
Hello ?
Hello , is this yours ?
That 's mine !
Should I bring it to you ?
No , don 't !
I 'm not wearing anything .
I 'll throw it to you .
Excuse me ?
Can you wait a bit ?
Thank you .
If not for your help , I 'd have been very embarrassed .
I was just passing by .
- You went fishing ? - Yes .
Would you like these ?
- For me ? - Yes .
There is no one to cook for me anyway .
I 'm not from here .
Where are you from ?
The city .
My name is Permana . Permana Sidik .
My name is Seruni .
Do you have family here ?
I did .
But not anymore .
Is your house far from here ?
Yes . I come here every morning and afternoon .
- Are you going back to the village ? - Yes .
Can I walk you home ?
It 's all right , thank you .
I have to go . Thank you for the fish .
Son of a bitch !
They 've started praying again . Murni !
That stupid headman has repented .
I need your help , Murni .
Destroy Sabri 's family .
I want to stop doing this .
This is how you repay me ?
What is happening ?
Honey ?
- What is going on ? - This is black magic , dear .
Go get Permana !
Oh God .
Son .
Permana .
Ma 'am ?
What 's wrong ?
It 's the headman .
Stay calm , dear .
Sir .
Will you recite the sura Al-Falaq with me ?
Don 't just hold in your pain .
Son of a bitch !
That Santri must die !
Did you get a lot of fish ?
Hi , Seruni .
Were you washing your clothes ?
- Yes . - Want to join me ?
- Sure . - You can use this .
Look !
- Isn 't it big ! - Yes !
Careful , pull !
Be careful ! Seruni !
Come here .
Hold on !
Are you okay ?
- Seruni ? Hey ! Seruni , don 't ! - Permana ...
Are you all right ?
Let 's go .
Oh dear God .
What if - -
You should go home .
No one is waiting for me .
Really ?
And no one ever will .
I saw it myself !
Maybe you were wrong , Darmo .
How could I be wrong ?
Even in the dark at night ,
I can still tell a 100-rupiah note from a 1,000-rupiah note .
This was in broad daylight !
To be honest , I 'm worried .
What if Permana is working with that queen of black magic ?
Or maybe he and Murni are working together to curse this village ?
That 's possible .
Because our powerful shaman , Kamdi ,
was defeated by Murni .
What could he do ,
if he were not the one who cursed us ?
Let 's be real .
Our situation right now
is messed up .
Listen .
Don 't act rashly .
We don 't have any proof .
We shouldn 't just ambush them .
I saw it myself . Isn 't that proof ?
No .
That 's an allegation .
If we all
see it ourselves ,
then that would be proof .
- Do you agree ? - Yes .
Good afternoon .
Afternoon .
What 's going on here ?
We 're
planning a gathering .
Oh , okay then .
I 'm going to the headman 's house .
- See you around . - See you .
A Santri like him cannot possibly be doing black magic .
Really ?
Do you know the saying ,
" A wolf in sheep 's clothing " ?
That 's dangerous .
Are you going to marry him ?
Not in this village .
I 'm going with him to the city .
He has a house there .
That 's your right .
But be careful .
Men are very clever with their words .
Remember Kohar ?
He was nice , too .
But it turned out that he was a playboy .
I 'm just saying ,
you need to make sure .
Baidah , please keep Permana company .
- All right . - I have some work to do .
- Someone asked me to write a letter . - All right , sir .
I 'll be right back .
Just hang out .
It 's still working hours for me .
All right , sir .
Your heart is aching with lust .
Your body misses the warmth of a man 's touch .
Hey .
I heard you 're going back to the city ?
Yes , if all goes well .
This Sunday .
This Sunday ?
So soon ?
Why ?
Do you not like it here ?
Are you lonely ?
You can call me .
You will find someone .
To tell you the truth , I have a girlfriend .
We 're getting married in the city .
Men are all liars !
Men are animals !
All the people here deserve to die !
Especially Permana and Baidah .
What 's wrong now ?
She took the love of my life two times .
She destroyed my hope two times .
I swear ...
on the devils in hell
that tonight ,
I will kill everyone in this village !
Oh God !
Oh no !
Get water !
Help him !
- Stand still ! - Please lie down .
Put out the fire !
It 's okay , calm down !
Calm down .
Please , recite the prayers I taught you .
I will face them outside .
All right .
Seruni ?
I 'm not Seruni .
I 'm Murni .
The queen of black magic .
I 'm here to kill you .
Murni ?
You 're Saijah 's daughter ?
How do you know my mother 's name ?
You 're just a snobbish city dweller .
You use your innocence to charm the ladies .
But I will not be fooled .
Wait .
That 's not important .
I just want - -
Murni !
Murni , wait !
I 'm your brother !
I 'm Kliwon , your big brother !
You were so small
when Mr. Maulana took me to Banten .
He made me one of his students .
I traveled so far away .
After that , we lost contact .
For years .
Don 't listen to him , Murni .
This is about winning or losing .
He 's just bluffing .
Believe me , I 'm your brother .
Murni , don 't do this !
What happened ?
We 're all just actors on this stage of life .
I don 't mind dying by your hand , my Permana .
My Kliwon .
Murni .
You 're my brother .
And my lover .
Watch out !
Fight him .
He 's the one who used me .
Help me .
Evil !
- Look out ! - No !
So , you 're the one behind all of this , Gendon .
Don 't be surprised , Sabri .
I 'm here because I lost .
I 've spent years training myself to destroy you .
Dozens of black magic teachers have taught me .
And now it is time for you to give the title of headman to me .
Otherwise , I will destroy this village .
Son of a bitch .
You plan to kill the people for not voting for you !
And you cursed my family just so you could become headman !
Sabri , let 's finish this , just the two of us .
Who deserves the title ? You or me ?
That has long been decided .
The people would never vote a son of a bitch like you in as headman .
Now , it 's between the authorities and a troublemaker who must be destroyed .
Son of a bitch .
You shall be destroyed , Sabri .
My sister .
Brother .